// Persia custom features

IDS_MSG_FACTION_AGING_CIVILWAR_WARNING5, "%{0}u is in danger. Because of its size and corrupted bureaucracy, internal forces can soon tear it apart unless drastic measures are taken. Opportunistic Satraps, some being former rulers of kingdoms %{0}u conquered, may well decide that their province would do better without your rule!~~You can entirely avoid this civil war through four means:~~- Being in a Golden Age~- Being a Glorious nation~- Having a small nation (25 regions or less in balanced difficulty)~- Having your average regional loyalty at 75 or higher~~Should none of these conditions apply, then you can mitigate the issue by not being old or decadent. Also, the more regions that have a loyalty of 75 or higher, the less impact the incoming civil war will have.",

IDS_MSG_FACTION_AGING_CIVILWAR_PERSIA, "%{0}u is torn apart as several Satraps (provincial governors) are rebelling. Persia often had revolts of such nature in its history, as the Satraps were given a lot of power and independence, given the extent of the empire. The direst ones were probably the 370 BCE revolts, where several governors revolted at once. It took 20 years for %{0}u to regain control of most of its empires, and its apparent weakness is said to have motivated Philipp II then Alexander the Great in they successful attempt in overthrowing the now fragile colossus.",

POP_HELLENIC_POW, "Hellenic Prisoners",

IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_GAINMONEY_ATH, "A merchant from %{0}u was suspiciously too successful in his trade with us, so we confiscated his merchandises. (+%{1}u money gained)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSEMONEY, "One of our merchant has been forced to surrender most of his goods when he reached a %{0}u city! (%{1}u money lost)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_GAINMETAL_ATH, "A %{0}u merchant has been seen stealing from us so he has been put to prison and his caravan is now our. (+%{1}u metal gained)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSEMETAL, "This is outrageous! For reason unknown, %{0}u has imprisoned one of our merchant and all his wares are confiscated! (%{1}u metal lost)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_GAINLEGACY_ATH, "The tyrant of a small border city decided to secede from %{0}u and is now openly pledging allegiance to us! (+%{1}u legacy gained)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSELEGACY, "An ill advised tyrant of a small border city has been fooled in accepting %{0}u dominion and is seceding from us! (%{1}u legacy lost)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_GAINSLAVE_ATH, "We found a group of spies, hidden among traveling citizens from %{0}u. They have all been put to work in our iron mines. (+1 Slave in capital)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSEPOP_YES, "Once again %{0}u is acting harshly against our citizens. They have arrested many of our traveling citizens on pretext they were spying on them! (Population lost)",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSEPOP_NO, "Once again %{0}u is acting harshly against our citizens. They have arrested several of our traveling citizens on pretext they were spying on them!",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_GAINWEAPONS_SPA, "A party of men from %{0}u has been captured as they were obviously spying on us. Their deadly weapons will be used to arm our soldiers.",
IDS_MSG_EVT_PERSIA_FRICTION_LOSEWEAPONS, "As they landed on the shore to resupply, the crew of one of our ship has been captured by  %{0}u! Most managed to escape their captors though.",

// IMPEDIMENTS
IDS_STRUC_NAME_IMP_Agrarian_Chiefdom, "Agrarian Chiefdom",
IDS_STRUC_TT_IMP_Agrarian_Chiefdom, "This is a regional impediment, a local site in the region with adverse effects on how easily you can develop this land.",



