IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE1, "Восстановление древней цитадели Картли",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT1, "Ходят слухи об очень древней цитадели в горах Картли, что расположены в древней Колхиде, также известной грекам под именем Гесперия. Если нам удастся восстановить могущественную крепость этого региона, то это подаст чёткий, что Колхида переродилась и вновь стала могущественной державой!~~Наш советник предупредит вас как только наши люди найдут подходящее место для её возведения.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE1, "Восстановление древней цитадели Картли в регионе Lacyzia",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT1, "Подходящее место для охраны важной долины найдено. Горные кручи предотвратят возможность лёгкого штурма нашей будущей крепости!~~Вам нужно возвести крепость в регионе %{0}u в течение %{1}u ходов, чтобы выполнить эту миссию.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE1, "Цитадель Картли завершена!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT1, "Мы справились! Работа была тяжела, как для наших граждан, так и для рабов, но новая цитадель была возведена, а её мощь и величие, которые она излучает, пошлёт сильный сигнал всем нашим соседям!~~Вы получаете 100 единиц наследия и безвозмездные очки культуры за эту миссию.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE1, "Время, мимолётное время...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT1, "Нам не удалось возвести новую крепость Картли в регионе Lacyzia. Нам стоит сконцентрировать наши усилия на других задачах...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT1, "Цитадель Картли в Lacyzia: У вас осталось %{0}u ходов чтобы её построить, если хотите получить дополнительные очки наследия и другие бонусы.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE2, "Create a merchant river-route",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT2, "We need a strong economy if we want to prosper. If we manage to trade with distant lands for their precious resources, then we can be rich, and much more powerful. It is rumored that distant Maurya and Balkh (Bactria) harbor spices, precious woods and stones.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as our merchants have found the proper locations for their trading posts.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE2, "Trading posts along the river-route",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT2, "Two regions would be appropriate for trading posts: %{0}u, in the vast steppes and Darband, in Bactria. We need to claim both of them within %{1}u turns to succeed in our endeavor.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE2, "We succeeded in establishing trading posts!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT2, "We have done it! We have established a trade network from Indus to Balkh, then Amu-Daria and Mtkvari! Our nation will be as rich as distant Carthage after such a feat...~~You gained 150 Legacy and free culture points in your capital for this mission. In addition a long term commerce benefit has been added to your nation (See Nation Panel).",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE2, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT2, "We did not manage to secure both regions necessary for our trade route. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT2, "Trading posts along the river-route: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE3, "Subdue our neighbors",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT3, "The elite from our main cities, Phasis and Dioscurias, have had enough of our troublesome neighbors. First there was their hill tribes raiding time and time the caravans of our Greek merchants, and now it is getting worse with harassment from nearby kingdoms.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as our nobles have decided upon a proper course of action.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE3, "Subdue Iberia",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT3, "Our main trouble comes from %{0}u and it has been decided that they must be subdued within %{1}u turns. We can achieve this goal in several ways: conquer them, make them a Client-state or even become their ally. It is up to you to use the sword or the quill in this task.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE3, "Iberia has been subdued!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT3, "It is done, in one manner or another, Iberia is no longer a threat and commerce can resume as before. What's more, the mountain tribes from our hinterland, the Svani and the Lazi, saw the might of our army and are joining its ranks!~~You gained 100 Legacy and free culture points in your capital for this mission. In addition 4 mountainmen warbands are joining your standing army.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE3, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT3, "We did not manage to conquer or subdue Iberia. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT3, "Subdue Iberia: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus units.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE4, "Subduing our neighbors",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT4, "The king is more and more worried about the growing power of the neighboring kingdoms. The noble and powerful Greek merchants also complain about the lost trade coming from this situation. Something must be done about that, and the king will decide rapidly about the best course of action.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as the king has decided who will incur the wrath of the powerful Kolchis army!~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE4, "Neutralize Armenia",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT4, "Our main trouble comes from Armenia (%{0}u), as they are growing in power. We can achieve this goal in several ways: have control of their capital, reduce them enough in size so they are no longer a threat or have them as a Client-State. It is up to you to decide which way will be the best, but it must be done within %{1}u turns.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE4, "Armenia has been neutralized!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT4, "It is done, one way or another, Armenia is no longer a threat and commerce can resume as before. The situation is still fluid but some Armenian nobles are willing to join us, in which manner, we don't know yet. Perhaps they will provide cataphracts, perhaps they will swear fealty...~~You gained 150 Legacy and free culture points in your capital for this mission. In addition an additional event involving the Armenian nobles will occur.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE4, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT4, "We did not manage to conquer or neutralize Armenia. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT4, "Neutralize Armenia: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effects.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE5, "Develop our country",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT5, "The semi-arid climate of our country is making the life of our peasants hard, as agriculture is barely sustaining the needs of our citizens. Something must be done about that, or we will stay as a backward nation.~~The King will ponder what must be done, and as soon as he has made up his mind, a counsellor will reach you with his instructions.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE5, "Irrigation works",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT5, "We can't be satisfied with the current state of our agriculture. The soils are either too dry in the hinterland, or swampy on the coast. For now on, we will focus on the plains we have and start some irrigation works. You need to build an irrigation canal in %{0}u to succeed within %{1}u turns.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE5, "Irrigation canal completed!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT5, "Water flows now freely between our fields, and soon the new harvest will arrive, like the cornucopia of old myths!~~You gained 100 Legacy and new farms will be set up for free in your nation.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE5, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT5, "We did not manage to bolster agriculture in our country. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT5, "Irrigation works: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effect.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE6, "Develop our nation",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT6, "As our cities grow, the need for more livestock increases. Construction materials are also in greater demand. Our country is made of vast forests and hills that could support extra wood cutting and herds of animals. The merchants are telling us they could make use of this lumber and the animals, leading to more profit and taxes for the nation.~~Once it has been determined what exactly would be best for Kolchis, a counsellor will reach you.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE6, "Animals and wood-cutting",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT6, "The Greek merchants from %{0}u are confident that they could make good use of up to two Shepherd Houses and two wood-cutting exploitations or sawmills. Build them where they will serve best in your nation within %{1}u turns and a reward will ensue!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE6, "Herding and timber exploitations built!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT6, "Our good people did not waste any time and with a judicious use of money grants and tax exemptions managed to build the required exploitations. This is also attracting workers from nearby regions in our nation.~~You gained 100 Legacy and two populations will be added in your nation.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE6, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT6, "We did not manage to build in time the shepherd hours and wood exploitations, too bad, the merchants speak of lost opportunities. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT6, "Herding and Timber: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effect.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE7, "Bad Lands, foul temper",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT7, "The King has been recently annoyed by insects of all sorts while touring his realm. Besides, he saw that many of the low lands were not fit for his people.~~The King will ponder what must be done, and as soon as he has made up his mind, a counsellor will reach you with his instructions.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE7, "Swamp draining",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT7, "Many of our lowlands are plagued with swamps which are of no use for our peasants. They must be drained, using techniques imported from Egypt or the west. You need to own 3 infrastructures buildings in %{0}u, they will prove useful for the workers who will have to dry these nauseous bogs. This should be done within %{1}u turns or the King will be quite displeased.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE7, "Swamp draining completed!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT7, "These useless lowlands around our cities are now safe for our peasants, and soon will be productive. More importantly, the King can now walk safely without being annoyed by pesky critters!~~You gained 100 Legacy and your region will gain more room to place buildings.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE7, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT7, "We did not manage to drain the swamps of our lowlands, as instructed. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT7, "Swamp Draining: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effect.",

IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TITLE8, "Might is right",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_START_TEXT8, "Once again the steppe peoples to our north prove to be a constant irritation for our nation.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as the king has decided how to best deal with these mounted warriors.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE8, "War against the Alains",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT8, "Our main trouble comes from the Alains, who are usually around %{0}u. Being nomads and raiders, they don't understand the concept of property, at least not if said property doesn't belong to them. We must first prepare our army, by having no less than 6 Military Buildings. And then we need to declare war to them, hopefully beating them soundly (if they are gone in the meantime, this will be sufficient for our purposes). This must be done within %{1}u turns.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE8, "The Alains should fear us!",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT8, "Our army is now ready, thanks to the training provided by our military infrastructure. We are ready to tackle the Alains. The King is pleased!~~You gained 150 Legacy and a general will lead the troops you have recruited.",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE8, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT8, "We did not manage to prepare in due time against the Alains. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_COLCHIS_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT8, "War against the Alains: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effect.",

IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TITLE1, "The rise of Mets Hayk",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TEXT1, "For too long we have been prey to our neighbors! But Armenia, ancient Mets Hayk, is fated for a greater destiny than to be the mere servant of another nation.~~Our counsellor will advise you as soon as the king as decided what is the best way for Armenia to be restored to her former glory.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE1, "Greater Armenia",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT1, "The time is right, or, at least, the King of Armenia has so decided. The kingdom should now expand to the east and to the west alike!~~You need to reach Civilization Level III (also named 'Empire') while having control of %{0}u regions, including the major harbor of Issus. You have %{1}u turns to achieve this mission.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE1, "Greater Armenia is born!",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT1, "Through military expertise and shrewd diplomatic skills, you have done it! An Empire is born, stretching thousands of kilometers across the land.~~You gained 250 Legacy, extra culture in your capital and the permanent modifier 'Expansionist' providing extra manpower.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE1, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT1, "We did not manage to expand enough our kingdom so it can become Greater Armenia. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT1, "Greater Armenia: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and bonus.",

IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TITLE2, "Master and Servants",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TEXT2, "Our nation is strong, but not strong enough. As it was done to us in the past, were we served Persia then the Seleucids, so shall others nations submit to our will.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as the King has decided who will have to pay homage to our nation.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE2, "King of Kings",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT2, "The king in his immense wisdom has decided that %{0}u nations must become our client-states, and in doing so provide us with a tithe. We need to achieve this goal within %{1}u turns to succeed in our endeavor.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE2, "Might makes right!",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT2, "We have done it! At least two nations are now our Client-states and are not doubt honored to serve mighty Armenia.~~You gained 250 Legacy, extra culture in your capital and a large amount of money has been delivered by the client-states.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE2, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT2, "We did not manage to have two or more client-states. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT2, "King of Kings: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus.",

IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TITLE3, "Between enemies",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_START_TEXT3, "Some neighboring empires are becoming stronger and stronger, and this worries the King. We might end up being the buffer between these warring giants.~~Our counsellor will warn you as soon as the king has decided upon a proper course of action.~~In addition to the counsellor notification, there will be an entry in the Reports tab of the Nation Panel.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TITLE3, "Rome and Parthia",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_TASK1_TEXT3, "These two nations are at best hostile to each other and are often at war. We must be clever so to not choose sides and end up supported the defeated faction. We should strive to reach %{0}u relationships with both of them within %{1}u turns. This won't be easy, as pleasing one will displease the other, but this is the safest course of action.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TITLE3, "Between giants",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_COMPLETE_TEXT3, "No small feat! We are now friends with both Rome and Parthia, and thus we can hope to stay outside their constant fighting!~~You gained 250 Legacy and free culture points in your capital for this mission. In addition as we are now ideally positioned to act as a commercial hub, several emporia are opening in our nation.",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TITLE3, "Time, fleeting time...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_PHASEOUT_TEXT3, "We did not manage to befriend both Rome and Parthia. We should concentrate our efforts on others things now...",
IDS_MSG_ARMENIA_MISSION_REMINDER_TEXT3, "Rome and Parthia: You have %{0}u turns left to achieve this mission, if you want to claim the extra Legacy and additional bonus effect.",.",